we're live with live vanilla gorilla
hello guys we're in Shanley Honda guys
hey we shout out to that person on
Twitter that told us where to go to find
a way mouth we just drove up and down
railroad for five minutes we found one
more like that
Wow Victor yeah this is totally visible
in the rear view mirror though yes
definitely reducing our lifespan until
the cops come the cops might come yeah
we might all end up to jail and we might
finish the finish carving Jamie yeah am
I gonna give up YouTube I hear when we
go to jail was that at least we want you
to fly yeah I were just gonna follow it
I didn't know they were hybrid they are
hybrid yes you can't have the future
without 38k why would the cops come
because some journalists followed a
conway mo for like two hours and the
cops came I saw what I saw they like
came
so we've tried to be low profile yeah we
have it this is such a power it's like
kind of residential we found a way took
away the one program this is way about 8
to10
you see on we are using again aren't you
and his rotary and he's not yes he is
but he is able to well you hit the way
no no we got to be under the radar here
yeah we wanna we want to slow the
profile but do you think they're
autonomous right now
hard to say oh it must be now they must
be yeah seems like this is like a that
hard no we haven't been a passenger in a
way mode they have it's like very
exclusive who allows is allowed to be a
passenger it's not just anyone you have
to sign an NDA you have to be a
volunteer so I think they have you go
through some I don't know some training
to be a passenger I have to sign an NDA
yeah not anymore seriously chastised the
drivers felt like a huge screen in front
of him they're gonna have to merge left
if we call the cops
we're not doing anything about they
fooled that rights you know they they
stopped it they change their mind
we following option now I'm taking over
Oh Eddie's say you know we can't do this
but they're just pulling over
because we're gonna go find them again
we're just gonna say we really need to
follow them
[Music]
[Laughter]
I mean we picked them up when they were
shopping that was the there's a lot of
McDonald's in the world there's like one
way mo that we've seen in Arizona all
right here we go
low profile up four above I mean we do
want to go right the only way you can go
is right so it's not she's wearing a
Santa hat oh that's so lovely
oh yeah honestly I do feel really bad
for the driver because I'd be a little
worried they'd be sketched out
especially with what's been going on
cancer Jesus Carol watch your language
Ron periscope oh my got two of them this
is amazing
we go to the left or that's gonna left
yeah let's let's wait okay okay okay I'm
just gonna slowly put my camera there so
take a look you guys you didn't see
anything
yeah should i film the more sketchy so
you have a very set like us the woman is
just way to us I think oh really
I'm not sure either way you know at some
point they're gonna have to embrace it
okay what are we doing why are we are we
just going next to them yeah no I can
get in the right leg
I mean we can say okay let me let me
film from the side then right what's the
fear right
they turned okay they're not coming I
don't see them but the other ones not
the other ones behind us no that's a bad
turn yeah where is it terrible
no way they can see them all right this
is silly
we're gonna get a restraining order for
them to not be within 500 feet we're
leaving very low-profile guys I don't
think they don't very fine okay why
don't why did we get so far away all
right I can make it slow down but this
is the same one I wanted to finally pull
over
come on yeah I can we flew a moment full
oh no the one behind us is the newer oh
I think they knew almost one in front
okay that's far away here we got a right
lane I can go super slowly okay yeah
just go super so
you can try to YouTube live no one goes
there so what said literally the worst
streaming service you guys could have
chosen that's
we can turn again and wait for it all we
find a new one what do we get milkshakes
shake yeah yeah we I mean wouldn't this
be so much more fun with milkshakes it
would feel more like this you look at
them in the eye and stuff your milkshake
yeah we also said we working on YouTube
live and I just directly went to
periscope I didn't even think about it
but you then Google will know where we
are that's why we can't that's what
we're using Apple maps people think
about it goes really slow in Arizona
guys like I can easily use my San
Francisco aggressive driving yeah you
laugh there's no problem well but they
have no traffic that's why right
yeah there's big looking but just floor
it and it tastes like it takes like a
second and a half yeah okay let's find
this waiver well because the tubule
works like I said up there yeah I guess
it also shifts slow yes yeah like the
Civic because of the CVT
[Music]
I got them engage open piloted sport
mode cool engage about sport mode here
we go how fun is that away no on an open
pilot don't be friends
yeah we're gonna have Chrysler supports
the Pacific or it drew is working yes
we're actually gonna support the guys
that we wait up in pilot yeah so drew
hits on a fun project I'm gonna do over
the holiday actually I mean I think we
should buy a minivan we don't have any
like more than five persons either
coming down and we rented positive there
today
I'll see if you can and then we are
gonna buy a Fiat 500x okay I was being
no you were just because it's Italian no
he also likes it okie does I do like
because he's Italian like he's like a
five-seater cars he said you know we
haven't been arrested yeah
about for a few cars we're trying to
remain not really well I
[Music]
everyone goes the speed limit and
Chandler why are we following huevos
because we have tourists you know
something what's the best feature for a
step and we are in traveling space and
you walk using a space that was like a
drug like I just broke randomly I mean
it had its brakes applied yeah that's
super picky about driving yeah yeah yeah
oh it's breaking for no reason great you
know why break the flow it I think
there's been maybe these 45 Americans
have a slightly fun look at exactly
might be going at 44 yeah white really
have been accurate although either
that's you have terrible those glasses
so they probably have to break when they
go faster than 45
oh you think gosh I would get so sick in
that part I'm breaking for this guy's
turning
sport
see there's always yeah the woman
doesn't even know where if he must get
followed all the time let's see if there
yeah I wonder if they always turn your
hands are on the wheel but definitely
driving she's just a really good safety
driver maybe we should give it a
shout-out to her as a safety they have
to keep their hands in
they're driving its own thing you know
those conspiracy theories that they say
it something doesn't happen something
everybody in the case of way more wine
it's actually true yeah it doesn't
excuse now do you think they'll be out
of business in five years do you agree
with my opinion it's a little
concessions
going down it's also possible that they
have a policy if they're being filmed
you should take over because they just
slow down to lose us we stopped next to
there's not a school unlike a
residential street like they definitely
know we were falling how do they know we
stopped next we stopped them into they
could but we were like two cars away no
no now but we've been following this
same car for sure yeah oh yeah they know
but then they didn't know
for why intentionally well guys they're
good these are going to everything you
say about two men driving a few years
it's just going to go the way of like
Google Fiber we should have driven s
them Eddie and you should have like put
both your hands like hey speed away real
quick I mean we could probably go back
you want to find McDonald or even like
something better do we want something
better than I take a better ricardo
loves Denny's who would have thought ok
yeah yeah
but that's Dave minutes we really should
have done that next to a way Moe what a
bummer
sorry guys no no I just thought about it
don't be sorry Eddie you did a wonderful
job finding that way no yeah yeah and
not getting us arrested yes it's fine we
can try I'm okay trying it for once
record are you sure it let's feel like
that was a lot of effort for users have
an open mind it was I was I tried
fighting in shakes it wasn't pin mine
have you tried in and out I guess
maybe we'll see another wave on the way
I'm still got 40 viewers Wow
I know people like the exciting what's
exciting I'm sorry we didn't follow
close I got this one that makes a movie
in very rude
so you okay yeah cool they're gonna find
out that way yeah and then Eddie just do
the hands up and then we'll call it a
time okay okay super cool oh all do
hands up
anyway mo bro down the way that roll
down the windows
right
it's pretty lame an update on what I
think they said HD maps should we talk
about their tweet we sleeping tonight
did you guys see the top like a counter
that counts down and every 30 seconds is
somebody but the thing about like I was
discussing this in the present like in
the little spoiler for people that are
still gonna I watch us and follow us on
the tour but like one thing one guy
asked a pretty good question about like
safety and I said how important is
safety for society cares it's very
important but when you think about still
driving like before you cannot compare
safety to to any other like average
driving you have to compare safety to
services that provide the same type of
service that car level 4 provides you so
when you take like a better car when you
take like public transportation the
level of safety is actually a lot higher
than the average driving so engage
it's not gonna be fair coming with the
average that I wear when you talk about
safety for level four yeah yeah just
because that because they're like a real
skilled driver like what are the tips
well you sound like what is driving you
somewhere well he's gonna like doing a
better job than what probably would do
if he's trying to buy himself yeah he's
getting worried job right people do
better and public transportation like
two trains right right super well I was
on the Muni though we hit a car and then
we had to stop and get out and wait for
the safety officer because we're on the
road on the end so like all of the
trains are backed up no one can get by
the car was fine we just like tapped on
the card room and let's go to hell for
trains it's great
I don't know how we hit a car but they
went away those terrible training
spirits are off there so just drive away
that wasn't even anything oh by the way
wave with it is not like we're driving
these are two faster oh yeah well it
full electric yeah I guess yeah by an
old otezla play of the pilot and
community are doing a super good job in
porting of the pilot to pre out the
pilot test
generous to me that his friend put it on
the boat with a bead oh oh really
[Music]
yeah you said they don't have a CC they
don't have never model a basis they can
ultimately break there is not as much
thank you Harold's still engage in any
changes
yeah just how many archive submit like
just just an audio track of the
periscope so is this one
thanks it's a huge these lanes are huge
no but the ones in the residential
thanks we'll try to keep being round so
that
at
they might get a single you gonna get a
secret am i leaving these cookies
probably rather not go through the drag
bird in and out like the line is so long
in the drive those who are curious and
seeing way most railroad was the way to
go
shut up to the person on Twitter who
gave us that to that okay also for those
listening and watching meet up tomorrow
Albuquerque fuse maker space 5 p.m. whoo
cool alright guys thanks so much